<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
                                <rss version="2.0">
                                <channel>
                                <title>Grab The Opportunity of Being a Small Business Owner in India</title>
                                <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com</link>
                                <description>India’s digital platform for latest news, industry updates, videos, policies, schemes, investment, funding and opportunities for small medium and micro businesses and enterprises</description><item>
                            <title>Towards Net-Zero Cities With Smart Buildings</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/towards-net-zero-cities-with-smart-buildings-34548</link>
                            <description>Pivoting to a Sustainable Future Sustainable smart buildings in cities are expected to represent a USD 24.7 Trillion investment opportunity by the turn of the decade, attracting significant ROIs.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1997756952.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-28 12:27:43</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Entrepreneurial Characteristics And Ideas in Turbulent Times</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/entrepreneurial-characteristics-and-ideas-in-turbulent-times-34547</link>
                            <description>The entrepreneur was looked upon from a diverse perspective as in his entrepreneurial behaviour. The function of the so-called entrepreneur was to welcome technology and hence be in a position to transfer that acquaintance into a tradable product.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1514554311.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-24 12:41:28</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>AgTech Projected To Grow To USD 35 Billion Market By 2025</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/agtech-projected-to-grow-to-usd-35-billion-market-by-2025-34546</link>
                            <description>India received $1 billion in Agritech funding between 2017 and 2020. Experiencing extreme interests from Investors side, India's agritech industry ranked third in terms of funding and number of start-ups after the USA and Germany.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1820154556.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-24 11:30:35</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Meesho Launches Campaign To Bring 4 Lakh Small Businesses Online</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/meesho-launches-campaign-to-bring-4-lakh-small-businesses-online-34545</link>
                            <description>Nearly 70,000 of suppliers are from Delhi on the other hand NCR has highest number of women sellers on the platform</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1816829259.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-24 09:59:24</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Will Metaverse Affect Small Business Of India?</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/will-metaverse-affect-small-business-of-india-34544</link>
                            <description>Small businesses, whether in India or at global level are said to experience a lot of profit with the concept of metaverse as it can help users to try and use the products virtually before buying them.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/854380881.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-23 11:21:02</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Goel Ganga Developments Launched Its Luxury Project Ganga Platinum At Pune</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/goel-ganga-developments-launched-its-luxury-project-ganga-platinum-at-pune-34543</link>
                            <description>With an investment of 200 Cr the project is spread across an impressive area of 5 lakh square feet with a limited-edition number of 215 palatial apartments</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1877124845.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-23 10:10:18</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>MSMEs And Startups To Benefit From India-UAE Trade Pact</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/msmes-and-startups-to-benefit-from-india-uae-trade-pact-34542</link>
                            <description>CEPA is expected to increase bilateral trade of goods and services to USD 100 billion and 15 billion respectively.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/52048093.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-02-23 09:13:22</pubDate>
                          </item></channel>
                                </rss>