<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
                                <rss version="2.0">
                                <channel>
                                <title>Grab The Opportunity of Being a Small Business Owner in India</title>
                                <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com</link>
                                <description>India’s digital platform for latest news, industry updates, videos, policies, schemes, investment, funding and opportunities for small medium and micro businesses and enterprises</description><item>
                            <title>Aakash BYJU'S Launches 'Education for All' To Empower Girl Child</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/aakash-byjus-launches-education-for-all-to-empower-girl-child-34975</link>
                            <description>The idea is to convert each of our centre in Aakash BYJU’S fast expanding network as a centre of excellence not only in coaching but also in inclusivity and women empowerment.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1593482608.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-11 10:11:13</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Strict Norms For Digital Lending Space Issued By RBI</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/strict-norms-for-digital-lending-space-issued-by-rbi-34974</link>
                            <description>latest regulatory framework is focused on the digital lending ecosystem of RBI’s regulated entities (REs) and the LSPs engaged by them to extend credit facilitation services.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1208245036.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-11 09:32:44</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>RBI Provides In-principle Approval to EaseBuzz for Payment Aggregation Authorisation</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/rbi-provides-in-principle-approval-to-easebuzz-for-payment-aggregation-authorisation-34973</link>
                            <description>According to RBI, "payment aggregators" are organizations that enable merchants and e-commerce sites to accept different payment instruments from customers in order to fulfil their payment obligations without the need for the merchants to develop their own separate payment integration system</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1561841805.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-11 09:20:44</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Amazon to Onboard 18,000 SMBs under 'Amazon Pay Smart Stores’ Program</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/amazon-to-onboard-18000-smbs-under-amazon-pay-smart-stores-program-34972</link>
                            <description>Amazon had launched this program two year back, in 2020, to smoothen the offline shopping experience of its customers and provide seamless credit to offline shoppers.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/872102238.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-11 09:11:44</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Raksha Bandhan: Siblings Build Businesses Together To Touch New Heights</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/raksha-bandhan-siblings-build-businesses-together-to-touch-new-heights-34971</link>
                            <description>“As kids we shared childhood memories, as grown-ups we shared a common vision and dream. It’s a privilege to be able to work in an environment of complete trust, support and unconditional love. We complement each other’s skills and are each other’s toughest critics,” Sonal Agarwal said.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1020621245.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-11 09:11:23</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>5G Innovations To Take Gaming Industry To New Level: Experts</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/5g-innovations-to-take-gaming-industry-to-new-level-experts-34970</link>
                            <description>The conclave outlined the industry’s vision for 2022 and beyond, with an eye on global and domestic trends, as well as India’s potential to disrupt the global industry in the near future.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1899610240.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-11 09:03:02</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Chinese Mobile Phone Companies To Comply With Govt’s Upcoming Guidelines To Stay In India</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/chinese-mobile-phone-companies-to-comply-with-govts-upcoming-guidelines-to-stay-in-india-34969</link>
                            <description>Chinese firms would have to agree to is broad-basing their distributor network, which is currently fully-owned by their own entities.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/596271475.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-10 11:52:49</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Dough & Cream Sets Up Another Store In Delhi</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/dough-cream-sets-up-another-store-in-delhi-34968</link>
                            <description>Dough and cream has been baking joyfully since 2018. In just four years, It has won over thousands of consumers by bringing them joy and making them fall in love with their delicacies. This bakery café has been running in ten sites lately.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1754576720.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-10 10:14:13</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>RBI Survey Shows How Much Median Inflation Perception Moderated</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/rbi-survey-shows-how-much-median-inflation-perception-moderated-34967</link>
                            <description>“CPI inflation in India breached the RBI’s 6 per cent tolerance limit for the fifth month in a row in June, marginally falling from 7.04 per cent in May. Now, the RBI survey suggests further moderation could be on the cards,” RBI said.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/117189683.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-10 10:10:54</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Ethanol Blending Can Reduce Imports: BPCL</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/ethanol-blending-can-reduce-imports-bpcl-34966</link>
                            <description>BPCL is setting up an integrated 2G and 1G Bio Ethanol Refinery at Bargarh, Odisha. The Bio-ethanol Refinery, which will increase the production capacity to about 6 Cr lit per annum of ethanol.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1297011410.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-10 10:04:05</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>UpGrad Raises USD 210 Million Fresh Funding</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/upgrad-raises-usd-210-million-fresh-funding-34965</link>
                            <description>The company said it is on track to record annual gross revenues of USD 400-500 million during FY23, of which about 45 per cent will be realised from its own-branded online courses and programmes.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/580702029.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-09 10:24:07</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Wealthtech Platform Dezerve Investments Raised USD 21 Million from Accel Partners</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/wealthtech-platform-dezerve-investments-raised-usd-21-million-from-accel-partners-34964</link>
                            <description>The Company did not disclose the distribution of stake that was given for this funding but stated that major stakes still belong to the founders and the team.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1442843763.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-09 09:29:22</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Buy Now Pay Later- A Business Rising From Good To Better</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/buy-now-pay-later-a-business-rising-from-good-to-better-34963</link>
                            <description>According to the new guidelines issued by the apex bank, nonbanks can no longer load prepaid instruments — digital wallets, or stored-value cards — using credit lines. The only valid options for a buyer are to prefill their wallet with cash, or to debit their bank or credit-card accounts.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/768055284.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-09 07:45:43</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>LetsVenture to Invest Around INR 80 Lacs in Start-ups with MeitY</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/letsventure-to-invest-around-inr-80-lacs-in-start-ups-with-meity-34962</link>
                            <description>The alliance will primarily invest in companies in several fields such as deeptech, gamingtech, fintech, and software-as-a-service (SaaS).</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/173618896.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-08 11:54:15</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Ola Electric Sales Down By 42 Percent In July, Know The Status Of Hero And Okinawa</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/ola-electric-sales-down-by-42-percent-in-july-know-the-status-of-hero-and-okinawa-34961</link>
                            <description>According to the report of the industry body, Federation of Automobile Dealers Association, the company sold 5874 vehicles in June. The report also mentioned that high inflationary pressure was one of the major causes for the downfall.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1431145534.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-08 11:49:06</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Over 1.5 Lakh Kiranas Opted For MSME Registration Since Inclusion Of Wholesale, Retail Trades</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/over-15-lakh-kiranas-opted-for-msme-registration-since-inclusion-of-wholesale-retail-trades-34960</link>
                            <description>As per the gazette notification dated June 27, 2017, the retail and wholesale activities were neither manufacturing units nor service units according to the definition of MSMED Act 2008. Hence, they were not able to secure the erstwhile Udyog Aadhaar Memorandum license to register as an MSME.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1660221267.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-08 11:44:19</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Export Of Agricultural Products Rises By 31 Per Cent: Govt</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/export-of-agricultural-products-rises-by-31-per-cent-govt-34959</link>
                            <description>The initiatives taken by the Agricultural and Processed Food Products Export Development Authority (APEDA) that works under the Ministry of Commerce and Industry have helped the country in achieving 31 per cent of the total export target in the first quarter of the current fiscal.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/20927771.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-08 11:01:38</pubDate>
                          </item><item>
                            <title>Need to put handloom census data in public domain: Piyush Goyal</title>
                            <link>https://opportunityindia.franchiseindia.com/article/need-to-put-handloom-census-data-in-public-domain-piyush-goyal-34958</link>
                            <description>The emphasis should be on onboarding of handloom weavers and handicraft artisans on the GeM portal in large numbers, while simultaneously making it incumbent upon all government departments to purchase handloom products for their textile needs.</description>
                            <image>https://franchiseindia.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/opp/article/english/images/1036629560.jpg</image>
                            <pubDate>2022-08-08 10:28:25</pubDate>
                          </item></channel>
                                </rss>